{
    "subject": "resource/Moloya_Goswami",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Moloya Goswami (Assamese: \u09ae\u09b2\u09af\u09bc\u09be \u0997\u09cb\u09b8\u09cd\u09ac\u09be\u09ae\u09c0) is a popular actress from Assam, India. She was the first Assamese actress to win the National Film Award for Best Actress for her performance in the Assamese film Firingoti (1992).",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Moloya Goswami is that she is a popular actress from Assam, India. She was the first Assamese actress to win the National Film Award for Best Actress for her performance in the Assamese film Firingoti (1992).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9402562379837036,
            "question": "What was the first Assamese film to feature an actress who won a National Film Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151560664176941,
            "question": "Is Moloya Goswami the only Assamese actress to have won a National Film Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8959691524505615,
            "question": "Which film earned Moloya Goswami the National Film Award for Best Actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8009324073791504,
            "question": "In what year did Moloya Goswami win the National Film Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7867553234100342,
            "question": "Where is Moloya Goswami from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7787085771560669,
            "question": "What award did Moloya Goswami win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567881345748901,
            "question": "What is Moloya Goswami known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6073309183120728,
            "question": "What type of award did Moloya Goswami receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5621890425682068,
            "question": "What field is Moloya Goswami recognized in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3501252830028534,
            "question": "Which country is Assam part of?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Moloya Goswami is that she is a popular actress from Assam, India. She was the first Assamese actress to win the National Film Award for Best Actress for her performance in the Assamese film Firingoti (1992).",
            "html": "dbpedia_8571_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Moloya Goswami recognized in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8571_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of award did Moloya Goswami receive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8571_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Moloya Goswami known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8571_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8571_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided context information confirms that Moloya Goswami is indeed a popular actress from Assam, India, and she won the National Film Award for Best Actress for her performance in the film \"Firingoti\" (1992)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}